<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TechMart15</string>

    <string name="title_section1">About Techmart</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Ad-War</string>
    <string name="title_section3">Code Trek</string>
    <string name="title_section4">Constructo</string>
    <string name="title_section5">Electromatrix</string>
    <string name="title_section6">Focus</string>
    <string name="title_section7">Hitz</string>
    <string name="title_section8">Ingenium</string>
    <string name="title_section9">Lan Gaming</string>
    <string name="title_section10">Full Throttle</string>
    <string name="title_section11">Pioneer</string>

    <string name="title_section13">Quizomania</string>
    <string name="title_section14">R.E.A.C.T</string>
    <string name="title_section15">Robo Bricks</string>
    <string name="title_section16">Reflux</string>
    <string name="title_section17">Rocket War</string>
    <string name="title_section18">Showbuzz</string>
    <string name="title_section19">Spelling Bee</string>
    <string name="title_section20">Tatva</string>
    <string name="title_section21">Treasure Hunt</string>
    <string name="title_section22">About The App</string>


    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_example">Example action</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="options_exit_text">Exit</string>
    <string name="textview1">TextView</string>
    <string name="textview2">TextView</string>
    <string name="textview3">TextView</string>
    <string name="images1">Image</string>
    <string name="images2">Image</string>
    <string name="images3">Image</string>
    <string name="images4">Image</string>
    <string name="adwar">Text</string>
    <string name="logo">Logo</string>
    <string name="refluxtextview1">Reflux tackles the problems that the industries and the society face that can be solved through major breakthroughs in chemical engineering. Students will come up with such solutions at Reflux.</string>
    <string name="refluxtextview2">Many environmetal and industrial problems have their solutions hidden somewhere in the books of Chemical Engineering.
One such problem that is both industrial as well as environmetal, is the coalfields in Jharia, Bihar which have been on fire
for the past 98 years. We invite all the chemical engineers to put their intelligence and knowledge in use to find out the most
feasible and plausible idea which might also become the solution to these ever-burning fire at Jharia which has claimed innumerous
lives in the district of Jharia along with depriving India of more than 4billion $ worth of coal deposits
</string>
    <string name="abouttechmarttext">Innovation requires the ability to collaborate and share ideas with people and the courage to challenge the old dogma and the conventional wisdom.</string>
    <string name="abouttechmarttext1"> We here at Techmart believe that innovation and courage lie at the very heart of entrepreneurship and we strive to kick start the chain reaction of transformation of ideas into real materialistic success. The motto of this year’s Techmart is “Startup India, Standup India”.
        It is a fortunate co-incidence that our goal aligns with the latest government schemes of promoting entrepreneurship among young engineers with innovative ideas. India needs a fresh minted idea that will start a revolution and turn India into a major manufacturing power. Techmart’15 provides a platform to showcase such innovation.</string>
    <string name="martian">Hello</string>
    <string name="martian1">While work on rockets that will get us to our red neighbor , whose allure as an otherworldly destination and potential host of alien life has deckoned scientists and dreamers for  thousand  of years, they are also thinking hard about how to build a sustainable colony on Mars. And since there is only so much space and weight on the rockets that will propel to mars, we need innovative solutions, not just solutions  available today, but solutions from years in the future when those Mars rockets will be ready.</string>
    <string name="martian2">Maintaining a colony on the Red Planet will prove to be a Leviathan challenge, compounded by the knowledge that should a catastrophe occur, “Help is only 140 million miles away”.</string>
    <string name="adwartext">AD-WAR requires the participants to be creative and develop a
marketing strategy for a product of their choice. Students will
perform an advertisement and thus present their advertising
idea. The best idea will bag the title of the ADKING.</string>
       <string name="treasure">“SEEK AND YOU SHALL FIND”</string>
    <string name="complexoman">Complexomania is a twist in engineering. Instead of solving a problem, complexomania asks the participants to introduce a complexity in it. A problem statement must be achieved in the most complex way for the participant to win the competition.</string>
     <string name="tatva1">Everything, anything, can be explained through a science that lurks in the nature. Through TATVA, we will discover the science behind materials, elements, their origins, their extraction, their applications. A series of tests will be put forward as challenges in front of the participants to test their knowledge in the field of metallurgy and material sciences.</string>
    <string name="tatva2">Tatvarequires the students to have an advanced understanding
of metallurgical processes. Students will face challenges related
to Metallurgical science and Engineering in a series of competitions.</string>
    <string name="wordamoment">The spelling bee competition initiates students into a world of competitive learning, acting as an invaluable tool for language improvement. The healthy competitive
spirit motivates the students to learn on their own without compulsion. The game and activity based nature of the competition ensures the students rapt attention and utilize their aspirations for winning games.
</string>
    <string name="wordam">A classic spelling bee competition that will ask
the students to hone their vocabulary and spell and
pronounce the given words correctly.</string>
    <string name="igni">“Ingenium”, the Latin for Talent, explores deep into students to find out their hidden talents in various competitive rounds. The finalists will perform in front of a panel of Judges who choose the winner based on the performances.</string>
    <string name="code1">A competitive programming challenge based on algorithms that tests the participant’s ability to code as quickly as possible and deliver the required output. The fulfilment of all the objectives in the least time decide the winner.</string>
    <string name="show1">The film festival of UIET Kanpur, SHOWBUZZ explores the artisticminds among engineers. The participants are required to shoot, direct and act in a short movie serving a noble cause that will be projected in front of an audience comprising of young students.
The creativity and director skills in the movie will decide the winner.</string>
    <string name="hitz1">Participants will go through a series of filtering challenges including
group discussions and personal interviews. HITZ requires the
participants to hone their communication skills in order to claim
the title of Mr./Ms.HITZ.</string>
    <string name="quiz">One of the biggest crowd pullers, Quizomania is a team
quiz that tests lateral thinking capacity.</string>
    <string name="rocket1">A competition of creating the perfect projectiles through
self made rockets that work on hydraulics principles.
fulfilments of the specific rules by the projectile hit will decide
the winner.</string>
    <string name="lan1">FIFA, Counter Strike, NFS Most Wanted!
        Enough Said!</string>
    <string name="em">A competition where students will design electronic
circuits on bread boards to perform various objectives given to them.</string>
    <string name="newsandupdates">News &amp; Updates</string>
    <string name="developed">Developed by: Vishal Anand</string>
    <string name="DSAU">Download News And Updates</string>
    <string name="tech15">Techmart15</string>
    <string name="adw">Ad-War</string>
    <string name="ct">Code Trek</string>
    <string name="cpml">Complexomania</string>
    <string name="costo">Research on Engineering and Advanced non Conventional Technology</string>
    <string name="elmtx">Electromatrix</string>
    <string name="fcs">Focus</string>
    <string name="hz">Hitz</string>
    <string name="rbso">Robo Soccer</string>
    <string name="ingn">Ingenium</string>
    <string name="lngm">Lan Gaming</string>
    <string name="oarna">Obstacle Arena</string>
    <string name="gridex">Grid Explorer</string>
    <string name="pnr">Pioneer</string>
    <string name="qzmna">Quizomania</string>
    <string name="rs">Real Steel</string>
    <string name="rflx">Reflux</string>
    <string name="rw">Rocket War</string>
    <string name="shbz">Showbuzz</string>
    <string name="ttv">Tatva</string>
    <string name="trhnt">Treasure Hunt</string>
    <string name="wamnt">Spelling Bee</string>
    <string name="versn">Version 1.0.0</string>
    <string name="adwarcordi1">-Kanak Balani</string>
    <string name="adwarcordi2">Shritansh Agarwal</string>
    <string name="round1">Round - I</string>
  <string name="adstring">Team of 3–6 members will present their product and convince through their act showing how powerful is their salability quotient. They must show a product in the act relating to their object of portrayal. The maximum time that will be allotted to each team for their act is 5 minutes.</string>
    <string name="round2">Round - II</string>
    <string name="adwarstring2">The teams that are selected move forward to this round comprises of viva slogan round. Each team will be asked 10–15 slogans. The best 6 teams of Round-II will move to Round-III. In case of a tie, a tie-breaker slogan will be asked, and the team that answers first moves to the next round. In case the team that answers first, do so incorrectly, the other team advances. A maximum time of 30 seconds will be given to the teams for each question. If the team fails to answer the question within the given time limit, the question will pass.</string>
    <string name="round3">Round - III</string>
    <string name="adwarround3">The best 6 teams that enter the final round will be given a product impromptu. They will be given a preparation time of 20 minutes to prepare their act. The act must have a runtime of 3–5 minutes. The teams that fail to report with their act within the 20 minutes prep time will be disqualified. The teams that fail to reach the venue will also be disqualified. The judges will decide the Top 3 winners from the acts that are presented in the final round.</string>
    <string name="prize">Prize:</string>
    <string name="prize1">1st Prize:</string>
    <string name="prize111">A shield will be awarded to the team leader. Certificates to each member with cash prize.</string>
    <string name="prize2">2nd Prize:</string>
    <string name="prize222">A silver medal and certificate to each members of the team with Cash prize.</string>
    <string name="prize3">3rd Prize:</string>
    <string name="prize333">A bronze medal and certificate to each members of the team with cash prizes.</string>
    <string name="email">Email:vishalanandl177@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="ayushgupta">-Ayush Gupta</string>
    <string name="codetrekinstruction">INTRODUCTION:</string>
    <string name="codetrekins">Code-Trek is the programming Contest of UIET Kanpur, organized by the TechMart team. It is a prestigious programming contest where each coder whacks his brain to code solutions to the given problems. It is the place where optimization and proficiency matters, skills matter, hard work matters, trying till the very end matters and winning loads of cash prizes matter.</string>
    <string name="eventpro">Event Proceedings:</string>
    <string name="in">Code-Trek is an on-the-spot programming competition. The event unfolds in 2 rounds:</string>
    <string name="is">I Round:</string>
    <string name="istround">•\tA preliminary written round to test your basic programming skills. </string>
    <string name="istround1">•\tThe test paper will consist of Aptitude and basic Coding questions.</string>
    <string name="is1">II Round:</string>
    <string name="istround11">•\tQualified teams can participate in this round only.</string>
    <string name="istround22">•\tThis round will consist of a practical competition in CSE Advanced Lab </string>
    <string name="codetrekrules">Rules and Regulations:</string>
    <string name="ct1">•\tA team can consist of at most 3 members.</string>
    <string name="ct2">•\tOnly teams of which all members are students currently registered in a university shall be eligible for prizes.  However, non-students are also welcome to participate.</string>
    <string name="ct3">•\tTop 10 teams will qualify for the II round</string>
    <string name="ct4">•\tPermissible languages are C, C++, Pascal, Python and Java</string>
    <string name="ct5">•\tCompilers to be used: gcc-4.3.2 for C, g++-4.3.2 for C++, fpc-2.2.4 for pascal, python-2.5 for Python and  javac-1.6.0_12 for Java.</string>
    <string name="ctju">Judgement Criteria:</string>
    <string name="ct6">•\tSolutions have to give the correct output for all the test data for a given problem to be deemed correct. There is no partial credit.</string>
    <string name="ct7">•\tAny team found to be indulging in any form of malpractice will be immediately disqualified.</string>
    <string name="ct8">•\tThe decision of the organizers in declaring the results will be final. No queries in this regard will be entertained.</string>
    <string name="ctprize">Prizes:</string>
    <string name="ctp">To be announced soon</string>
    <string name="hitzc1">-Shruti Srivastava</string>
    <string name="hitzc2">Saurabh Sharma</string>
    <string name="hitzr1">Round-1 (Introduction and Group Discussion):</string>
    <string name="hitzr1d1">•\tA brief introduction in 5 lines in which the candidate has to describe their own self (at the start of group discussion)</string>
    <string name="hitzr1d2">•\tA round of group discussions (5 candidates at a time).</string>
    <string name="hitzr1d3">•\tFiltration will be done by the coordinating team.</string>
    <string name="hitzr1d11">•\tCredit point to the candidate who initiates the discussion</string>
    <string name="hitzr1dd1">Criterion of Filtration:</string>
    <string name="hitzr1d22">•\tLogics and facts</string>
    <string name="hitzr1d33">•\tClarity of speech, postures, selection of words, temperament.</string>
    <string name="hitzr2">Round-2 (Situation and Reaction):</string>
    <string name="hitzr2d1">•\t10 Girls and 10 Boys will be filtered after round-1</string>
    <string name="hitzr2d2">•\tA situation will be given to each candidate to which they will be supposed to give a tactful and feasible reaction.</string>
    <string name="hitzr3">Round-3 (Personal Interview):</string>
    <string name="hitzr31">This being the final deciding round, will be judged by the panel composing of faculty members only.</string>
    <string name="hitzro"><![CDATA[Proposed panel---->\n•\tMr. Puneet Malhotra]]></string>
    <string name="hitzp">Prize:</string>
    <string name="hitzpd">The winners will be awarded the title of Mr.Hitz and Ms.Hitz. \nCash prizes worth Rs 3000 shared by both winners with certificate of excellence and sash with gift hampers.</string>
    <string name="hitzex">Expenses:</string>
    <string name="refluxco">-Deepshikha Shukla</string>
    <string name="refluxco1">Diksha Tiwari</string>
    <string name="refluzeventd">Event details:</string>
    <string name="refluxevedis">Department of Chemical Engineering, UIET Kanpur is proud to present its Technical event REFLUX. We call it our annual celebration of the spirit of Chemical Engineering rather than just a Technical Festival. It holds the motto of promoting science and technology, scientific thinking, and innovation in the field of Chemical Engineering. \nREFLUX provides an opportunity to all the budding chemical engineers to compete, exchange ideas, collaborate and learn and of course have fun all under the same roof.</string>
    <string name="refluxeven">Events:</string>
    <string name="refluxch">•\tPoster Presentation\n•\tChe Q\n•\tChem innovate</string>
    <string name="refluxevent">Problems to be discussed:</string>
    <string name="refluxev">•\tPollution\n•\tWater treatment</string>
    <string name="refluxJudges">Judges:</string>
    <string name="refluxjudgesname">•\tDr. B.P. Singh\n•\tDr. Brishti Mitra</string>
    <string name="refluxcordiinfo">Coordinators:</string>
    <string name="refluxcordiin"><![CDATA[•\tDeepshikha Shukla----------------->8416816214 \ndeepshikhashukla18@gmal.com \n•\tDiksha Tiwari----------------------->9559064404 \ndikshatiwari4007@gmail.com]]></string>
    <string name="refluxprize">Prize Money:</string>
    <string name="refluxp">•\t1st Prize:- Rs 2000/-\n•\t2nd Prize:-Rs 1000/-\n•\t3rd Prize:-Rs 500/-</string>
    <string name="sbcord">-Tanvi Tripathi</string>
    <string name="sbinfo">SHOWBUZZ, UIET’s own film festival motivates the top storytellers let their ideas flow freely on the moving storyboard. It’s the platform for next Arunabh Kumar and Biswapati Sarkar to firm their feet into the field. SHOWBUZZ is one event which brings all the technical and creative talents in one reel and gives a screen to project the works of the best directors, video editors, audio mixers, storytellers, actors, and etcetera. \n“A camera in one hand and a good script in the other makes it possible for storytelling to come to life. Sometimes the stories are already in our minds and we have the entire scenes worked out, but they never come out. SHOWBUZ lets the doors wide open.\n” So gather your gear, and start capturing the imagination into the lenses.</string>
    <string name="sblca">LIGHTS CAMERA ACTION!</string>
    <string name="sbrule">Rules:</string>
    <string name="sbrules">•\tThe participants must carry their registration slip to the event venue. Participation will not be allowed without proof of registration.\n•\tThe movies should not have a runtime of more than 15 minutes an less than 10 minutes. \n•\tThe movie making team must not contain more than 6 members. There can be any number of actors but the credits must include only the original movie making team. \n•\tThe movie must not contain any explicit content that can be harmful to society. \n•\tThe movies should not contain or promote any kind of unethical behavior. \n•\tViolence, blood and foul language is strictly prohibited. \n•\tMovies can be of any genre. \n•\tOne team can submit more than one movie but each movie must be registered separately. \n•\tThe movies must be submitted digitally only in (.mp4) format \n•\tOriginality will be appreciated \n•\tThe movies must be submitted before or at 5:00 PM on 19th November, Thursday. \n•\tThe decision of the event coordinators and the judges will be final.</string>
    <string name="sbevalu">Evaluation criteria:</string>
    <string name="sbcri">The movies will be evaluated based on the following criteria:</string>
    <string name="sbc">•\tTitle of the movie- The title of the movie should be descriptive an no longer than 5 words. \n•\tDirection \n•\tPlot of the movie \n•\tActing \n•\tSound and visual effects</string>
    <string name="sblast">The event coordinators will judge all the submitted movies and the best 5 movies will be played in front of the UIET audience and a panel of judges in lecture hall- 1.</string>
    <string name="coordinator">Coordinator:</string>
    <string name="pooja">-Pooja Tiwari</string>
    <string name="tavd1">Day-1 (Screening)</string>
    <string name="tavd1d1">All the registered teams will participate. A team can have a 2 or 3 members.</string>
    <string name="tatd1d1d1">Round-1: Material Science Vocabulary Test:-</string>
    <string name="tavad1t1"><![CDATA[•\tParticipants will be presented with crosswords puzzles. \n•\tNo negative markings \n•\tNumber of questions asked:20]]></string>
    <string name="tatvad1">Round-2: Table Top Quiz Round:-</string>
    <string name="tatvad2dis"><![CDATA[•\tA series of questions will be presented to all the participating teams and the answers will be recorded on the paper by one of the team members. \n•\t+2 for each correct answer. \n•\t-1 for each wrong answer. \n•\tNumber of questions asked--->30]]></string>
    <string name="tavtd2mainevnt">Day-2 (Tatva Main Event):-</string>
    <string name="tatdisd2">Six teams from the screening round will qualify for the Tatva main event. \nDay-2 will have 4 rounds in a span of 1 hours 30 minutes.</string>
    <string name="tavtd2r1">Round-1: (Video Round):-</string>
    <string name="tatd2r1d">•\tA 10 seconds video clip will be shown to each team and a question will be asked based on that clip. \n•\tEach correct answer carries 20 marks. \n•\tIf a team fails to answer the question prompted to them, the question will not be passed to any other team. \n•\tNo negative markings.</string>
    <string name="tavtcrac">Round-2: (Crack The Clue):-</string>
    <string name="tavtcrd"><![CDATA[•\tEach team will be presented with a question. \n•\tHints can be asked for. Every time a hint is asked for, the reward of the question decreases. \n•\tWithout Clue-------> 40 marks \n•\t1st clue---------------> 30 marks \n•\t2nd clue--------------> 20 marks \n•\t3rd Clue--------------> 10 marks \n•\tOnce a clue has been asked for, the teams will be awarded negative points in case of no or wrong answer.]]></string>
    <string name="tavtd2r2">Round-3 (Color Lottery):-</string>
    <string name="tact">•\tColours will be shown on the screen. Each colour will have a specific question and specific points hidden behind it. \n•\tThere will be four bonus colours with extra marks hidden behind them. \n•\tThere is no negative marking for ordinary colours which carry a question of 10 marks \n•\tBonus colours carry questions with 40 marks but there will be a risk of losing 10 points in case of wrong answer. \n•\tBonus questions cannot be passed.</string>
    <string name="tavtad2r2d2">Round-4: (Wipeout Round):-</string>
    <string name="tavtalast">•\t10 consecutive questions will be asked to each team. \n•\tEvery question will carry 10 marks. \n•\tTeams can decide to skip a question but in case of a wrong answer all the marks obtained via previous questions of the round will be wiped out</string>
    <string name="anup">Anup Mishra</string>
    <string name="anu">Quiz Master:</string>
    <string name="tavtacontact">Contact:</string>
    <string name="tavtacon">7269962070 \nEmail:ptiwari1403@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="tavtavol">Volunteers: \nPiyush (MSME) \nShwetank Dubey (MSME) \nAayush (MSME)\nContacts: \nAnup Mishra\n(+91)8896410698</string>
    <string name="constcord">Apurva Ghosh\nShikha Kumari\nHimanshu Singh</string>
    <string name="deputy">Deputy Coordinator:</string>
    <string name="dep">Deepshikha Shukla\nShivani Singh\nPriya Pathak\nAnoop Jaiswal</string>
    <string name="con">Here is your chance to prove mettle as an innovation engineer and show the world how miraculous adding a few strings to the construction of a popsicle bridge with glue can be.</string>
    <string name="regi">Registration:</string>
    <string name="reginfo">•\tTeam registration are invited only\n•\tA team of 3 to 5 members is allowed</string>
    <string name="r1">1st Round:</string>
    <string name="r2">2nd Round:</string>
    <string name="r1info">A team will be taken based on basic mechanics</string>
    <string name="r2info">Selected teams will have to design a cable stayed suspension bridge using popsicle sticks, cotton string and fevicol that can sustain the maximum possible load with minimum deflection satisfying the understated constraints.</string>
    <string name="conp">1st Prize: 1500 Rs.\n2nd Prize: 1000 Rs.\n3rd Prize: 500 Rs.</string>
    <string name="remarks">Remarks:</string>
    <string name="rem">•\t1 day event (2 hours approx for model making, 15 to 20 minutes for quiz)\n•\tCertificates to all the participants.\n•\tEquipments needed for the model will be provided.</string>
    <string name="ss">Shivani Singh</string>
    <string name="sb">Swati Bhagtani</string>
    <string name="tr1">A team of 4 or 5 members will be given a task and clues, roaming around the campus the team completion the task in minimum time will come up as a winner.</string>
    <string name="tr2">•\tA team is to be registered (Individual participants are not allowed).\n•\tTeam must have 4 or 5 members minimum and maximum 6 members.</string>
    <string name="round">Round:</string>
    <string name="tr3">A 3 round event, treasure will be disclosed in 3rd round.</string>
    <string name="tr4">1st Prize (Treasure): 2000 Rs.\n2nd Prize: 1000 Rs.\n3rd Prize: 500 Rs.</string>
    <string name="tr5">•\tOne day Event\n•\tNeeds 2 hours approx\n•\tCertificates to all the participants (2nd round onwards)\n•\tMedals and Shields to winners.</string>
    <string name="co">Contacts:\nShivani Singh: (+91)8858069026</string>
    <string name="aj">Anoop Jaiswal</string>
    <string name="pp">Priya Pathak</string>
    <string name="ag">Apurwa Ghosh</string>
    <string name="sst">DeepShikha Shukla\nShivani Singh</string>
    <string name="q1">The event tests how much participants is conscious about what is going around the globe. Event  comprises of  screening and buzzer round, 4 or 5 teams are advanced to final round.</string>
    <string name="q2">•\tYou can register as a team only.\n•\tA team of 3 to 5 members will be considered.\n•\tRegistration fee: 40 Rs. per head.</string>
    <string name="q3">All the registered team will answer 20 questions asked to them through PPT, or orally.</string>
    <string name="q4">•\tTwo day event (one round each day).\n•\tCertificates will be given to all the 2nd round participants and medals to winners.</string>
    <string name="fdisc">TECHMART (UIET-KANPUR) is pleased to announce a photography contest for school / college students. Open to all, here is a chance to showcase your work.</string>
    <string name="sandeep">Sandeep Bhargava</string>
    <string name="fc">RULES OF THE PHOTO CONTEST FOCUS (PIXELS):</string>
    <string name="rules">Rules:</string>
    <string name="f1">•\tBy submitting any entry to this contest, you accept these terms and conditions.\n•\tTHEME: SELFIE WITH WATER and CANDID PHOTOGRAPHY. Shoot anything that represents water and real life moment.\n•\tFORMAT FOR SUBMISSION:\n(i) Each participant may submit up to 2 photos from each category. No photo may be more than 5 MB in size
\n(ii) Merited entries will register for the Final round where they will be asked to click a photograph based on a theme which will be unveiled impromptu and submit the same to the event coordinator within 30 minutes of unveiling of the theme.
\n•\tHOW TO SUBMIT: \nSend the images by email to sandeep.bhargava@rocketmail.com OR Whatsapp +918802727423 with the subject line: Photo Contest. Each email may have only one photo. In the main body of the email, enter the following details: Name, Date of Birth, Email, Contact Tel / Mobile, School / College, Grade / Class / Year, Caption for Photo.\n•\tWHO MAY PARTICIPATE? \nThe contest is open to students from schools and colleges all over India. Management, owners, employees and the family members.\n•\tDEADLINE FOR SUBMISSIONS: \n11:59 p.m. on November 17, 2015, Indian Standard Time. The organizers reserve the right to extend the contest duration by a period of not more than 15 days. Entries received after the submission deadline will not be considered. UIET will not be responsible for any entries delayed or lost in transit. UIET reserves the right to cancel the competition at any time, without prior notification or obligation, for any reason.</string>
    <string name="f2">Final round participants shall be given Certificate by the University and the winners will be suitably rewarded.</string>
    <string name="judging">Judging:</string>
    <string name="f3">Shortlisted images will be judged by an eminent panel comprising those who understand and appreciate the art of photography, and will base their opinion on pure merit only. The final results will be declared on 20th November after contest deadline ends. The decision of the judges will be final and binding on all participants.</string>
    <string name="f4">ALL MERIT ENTRIES MAY FEATURE ON tech-mart.in:</string>
    <string name="f5">Participants will have to give their consent for their entries to be posted on techmart.com on any related accounts or sections set up on Flickr, Facebook, Google+ and other social media and image sharing websites.. Entries may be posted at any stage of the competition and will be open for anyone to see. Suitable credit will be given. Participants have the option to have their one line bio, contact information and web / blog address to be given in the credit line.</string>
    <string name="f6"><![CDATA[ORIGINALITY & COPYRIGHT:]]></string>
    <string name="f7">All submissions must be genuine photographic images that are recognizable and not a completely created image. Digital retouching is allowed though restricted solely to simple colour correction and cropping. Digitally manipulated images will be disqualified. Images need not be digital, and can be sent as scanned images. The participants are required to submit their www.exifdata.com (This site gives you the information about every detail of your picture) screenshot on the above specified e-mail id. All work must be original. Contest participants must affirm that submissions are their original work and that they are the holder of the copyright or that they have the right to copyright any and all photographs submitted to this contest.</string>
    <string name="web">For More Information, NEWS and Updates Visit: www.tech-mart.in</string>
    <string name="vishalanand">Vishal Anand</string>
    <string name="reactintro">"The word that we have created as a result of the level of thinking we have done thus far, creates problems that cannot be solved at the same level of thinking at which we create them."</string>
    <string name="react1">Research in Engineering and Advanced non Conventional Technology (R.E.A.C.T) is a platform for the young pioneer of Engineering.To review these researches, find application for the same.</string>
    <string name="st">Structures:</string>
    <string name="react2">Submission of review papers.\nParticipants must email their review papers to "reactintechmat@gmail.com" with their registration number.</string>
    <string name="react3">Presentation\nThe finalists will be called to explain their review papers in front of the judges along with a powerpoint presentation.</string>
    <string name="react4">•\tThe review papers must be completely original. Contact from internet can be considered as source but a copy will not be entertained.\n•\tParticipants must submit their review papers along with their name and registration number through email at "reactintechmart@gmail.com".\n•\tThe deadline for submission is 2:00 PM, 8th November 2015.\n•\tParticipants need to submit a hard copy of their review paper to the student coordinator by 8th November\n•\tParticipants need to mention the reference from where they have taken the data.</string>
    <string name="topic">Topics:</string>
    <string name="react5">•\tLeap Motion\n•\tVirtual Reality\n•\tAutomatic Air Suspension System\n•\tAlcohol as Alternative fuel in I.C Engines\n•\tCloud Computing\n•\tCyber Security\n•\tFuel Cell Technology\n•\tRadioactive Waste Management\n•\tSignal &amp; Image Processing\n•\tWireless Communication &amp; Mobile Computing\n•\tLow Power VLSI Design\n•\tSurvival Strategies on Mars</string>
    <string name="ep">Event Proceeding</string>
    <string name="react6">All submitted review papers will be screened by the Technical Committee and the merited participants will be forwarded to final round of the presentation where the finalists will present their review paper in front of the Technical Committee with the help of a powerpoint presentation.</string>
    <string name="react7">Authors of the review papers will have to register on or before 5:00 PM, 8 November 2015\nParticipant fee: Rs. 100\-\nThe participants must submit a soft copy as well as a hard copy of the review paper at the time of registration. The soft copy must be through an email to "reactintechmart@gmail.com".</string>
    <string name="date">Important Dates:</string>
    <string name="react8">•\tLast Date for submission of Full Paper: 8 November 2015\n•\tLast Date for Registration of the Author: 8 November 2015\n•\tNotification on Selection of Papers: 16 November 2015\n•\tEvent Date: 20 November 2015</string>
    <string name="react9">Total prize worth 6000 Rs. to be shared by all the winners.</string>
    <string name="vishalinfo">Contact:\nVishal Anand (Student Coordinator):\n(+91)8009417767\nEmail: vishalanandl177@gmail.com\nShakti Katiyar: (+91)8005017517</string>
    <string name="tc">TECHNICAL COMMITTEE:</string>
    <string name="tc1">•\tDr. Brishti Mishra\n•\tDr. R.N.Katiyar\n•\tDr. Richa\n•\tDr. U.C.Sharma\n•\tDr. Anuj Dixit\n•\tDr. V.K.Kashyap\n•\tDr. Niyati Padi\n•\tEr. Vishal Awasthi\n•\tEr. Alok Kumar\n•\tEr. Hemant Kumar\n•\tEr. Amitesh Anand\n•\tEr. Arpit Srivastava\n•\tEr. Md. Zeeshan</string>
    <string name="oc">ORGANIZING COMMITTEE:</string>
    <string name="tc2">•\tEr. Parul Awasthi\n•\tDr. Richa Verma\n•\tEr. Ajeet Kumar Srivastava\n•\tEr. Amit Katiyar\n•\tDr. Poonam Dixit\n•\tEr. Atul Kumar Agnihotri\n•\tDr. Prabal Pratap\n•\tEr. Ajeet Pratap Singh\n•\tDr. Deepti Agrawal\n•\tEr. Md. Shah Alam</string>
    <string name="tc3">•\tVishal Anand\n•\tShakti Katiyar\n•\tPratibha Singh\n•\tMd. Shahbaaz\n•\tVijya Laxmi Anand</string>
    <string name="sc">STUDENT COMMITTEE:</string>
    <string name="rocket2">Fire up your fellow students, assemble a team of rocket scientists, bombard your science teacher until she or he registers! Come have a blast-off and launch your summer in style!\nAnd hey, it really is rocket science.</string>
    <string name="sk">Shubham Kanaujia</string>
    <string name="vs">Vidya Sagar</string>
    <string name="ankur">Ankur Yadav</string>
    <string name="pio">Pioneers event is about startup idea. Participants get their hands dirty and put theories to the test by collaborating with like-minded. It’s important to remember that it’s not just about framing the idea—it’s about the how to achieve that idea ,it’s about the right team that solve real-world problems.</string>
    <string name="format">Format:</string>
    <string name="pio1">There will be two rounds; participants selected in round1will pitch their idea in second round.</string>
    <string name="pio2">Hardcopy of idea has to be submitted by participants on/before 19th November.\nIdea may be presented by from any category mentioned below-</string>
    <string name="pio3">•\tDeveloper-\nRuby On Rails , PHP ,Google Developers ,Java developers ,.NET ,CSS, Android Developer, iPhone Developer, iPad Developer, Python, JQuery, Drupal, Django, Silverlight, Dreamweaver, HTML, WordPress, Cloud ComputingWeb Design / Refresh\n•\tDesigner\n•\tBusiness/non-technical\nA participant may have different idea from above mentioned category.</string>
    <string name="pio4">Teams form organically around the ideas and the selected team will carry on 2nd round.\nMaximum Four teams from the 1st round will qualify for the Pioneer main event.\nParticipants have to pitch their idea to judges.\nMaximum time each participating team/individual can take-20min.\nTotal time duration for 4 teams-1hr 20min</string>
    <string name="pio5">Event Judging Criteria:</string>
    <string name="pio6">The idea will be evaluated based on the following criteria:\n•\tCustomer Validation :\nAre teams building something that people actually want? How well does the team understand their customer and their customer’s needs?\n•\tExecution and Design\nHave they established a minimum viable product , such as software or hardware, etc.? Did they build the minimum set of features needed to start collecting data? Does it deliver a compelling and captivating user experience? Were they able to demo something functional?\n•\tBusiness Model Validation\nHow does the team plan on making this a successful business? Have they thought about (either solved or identified problems) competition, how to scale, acquiring customers, their revenue model etc? How will they acquire their first 100 customers?</string>
    <string name="pio7">Rules and Guidelines:</string>
    <string name="pio8">•\tIdea should be presented in A4 sheet can be hand written or  printed.\n•\tThe idea should not be more than 750 words( 3 A4 sheets).\n•\tTeam size 1–3.\n•\tThe  content should not contain or promote any kind of unethical behavior.\n•\tA team/participant can submit more than one idea but must be registered separately.\n•\tOriginality will be appreciated.\n•\tThe idea must be submitted before or at 5:00 PM on 19th November, Thursday.\n•\tPresentation at/on 19th November, Friday.\n•\tVenue- IT seminar hall.\n•\tParticipant  may use PPT slides for presentation.\n•\tThe decision of the event coordinators and the judges will be final.</string>
    <string name="pio9">•\tParticipation certificate will be provided to each participant.\n•\tWinner Prize money - (will be declared on event date )  and Winning certificate
</string>
    <string name="seva">Sevanand Yadav</string>
    <string name="spsm">Sushmita Pandey\nSakshi Mehlotra</string>
    <string name="piocon">Contacts:\nSevanand: (+91) 8416839963\nEmail: sevanandyadav@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="codecon">Contacts:\nAyush Gupta: (+91)9720449004\nAnkur Yadava: (+91)8574962672</string>
    <string name="adcon">Contacts:\nShritansh Agrawal: (+91)8756112491\nKanak Balani: (+91)9456025896</string>
    <string name="focuscon">Contacts: \nSandeep Bhargava \n(+91)8802727423\n Facebook: \nwww.facebook.com/Pixels.UIETK</string>
    <string name="constcon">Contacts: \nApurwa Ghosh: (+91)8176008499\nHimanshu Singh: (+91)9167812509</string>
    <string name="ds">Divya Singh</string>
    <string name="econ">Contacts:\nDivya Singh: (+91)9456062533</string>
    <string name="ssingh">Savakrit Singh</string>
    <string name="vt">Vidit Tiwari</string>
    <string name="ingcon">Contacts:\nAnup Mishra (+91)9450753808\nVidit Tiwari: (+91)9838601204</string>
    <string name="vy">Vivek Yadav</string>
    <string name="vivek">Contacts:\nVivek Yadav: (+91)9451925931\nEmail ID: thevivek@live.com</string>
    <string name="ajaisa">Contacts:\nAnup Jaiswal: (+91)9616202185</string>
    <string name="subhaminfo">Contacts: Shubham Kanaujia: (+91)8896530582</string>
    <string name="sub">Contacts:\nShivam Singh: (+91)8896915722</string>
    <string name="spel">Contacts:\nPrakhar Mittal: (+91)9456062533\nVidit Tiwari: (+91)938601204</string>
    <string name="pm">Prakhar Mittal</string>
    <string name="vtieari">Vidit Tiwari</string>
    <string name="uiet">UIET Kanpur</string>
    <string name="te">Presents</string>
    <string name="venue">Venue:</string>
    <string name="csjmu">UIET, CSJM University Kanpur\nPincode: 208024</string>
    <string name="team">TECHMART 2015 Official Team:</string>
    <string name="teamname">•\tChairperson:\n\tPrateek Srivastava (CHE)\n\tSavakrit Singh (CSE)\n•\tVice-Chairperson\n\tPrakhar Mittal (IT)\n•\tSecretary:\n\tVijaya Laxmi Anand (CHE)\n\tShubham Sahu\n\tDivya Singh (ECE)\n•\tEvent management:\n\tVidit Tiwari (CHE)\n\tPraneet Mishra (CHE)\n•\tMedia &amp; Promotions:\n\tKanak Balani\n\tAmrit Jaiswal\n•\tInauguration:\n\tShivam Singh\n\tNitish Bakshi\n•\tWebsite committee:\n\tYashi Mishra\n\tChandni Yadav\n•\tExternal affairs:\n\tUtkarsh Rastogi\n\tSaurabh Sharma\n\tMohd.Shahbaz\n\tAnurag Kumar\n\tPrabuddh Bharat\n•\tTechnical management:\n\tVishal Anand\n\tShakti Katiyar\n•\tRegistration:\n\tMohammad Saleem\n\tSonu Kumar\n•\tHospitality:\n\tDiksha Singh</string>
    <string name="abt">•\tEr.  Parul Awasthi (Convener, Techmart)</string>
    <string name="shakti">Shakti Katiyar</string>
    <string name="lan2">Lan gaming is the most wanted event of techmart for gamers and also who are looking for fun. With multiplayer gaming, the fun of gaming is not only evovled but increased manifolds. Lan_Gaming organized under the techfest of UIET, Techmart, comprises of 3 games and and is a 2 day event.</string>
    <string name="lan3">No One Can Stop You Once You Are Determined To Win The Race</string>
    <string name="lan4">Games:</string>
    <string name="lan5">1.\tNeed for Speed Most Wanted.\n2.\tFIFA 2011\n3.\tCounter Strike Condition Zero</string>
    <string name="day1">Day 1:</string>
    <string name="lan6">On very first day of techmart, gamers will take part and winners for each round in each game will be decided on the spot. Winners qualified for the final round will then compete for the first place in final round on next day.</string>
    <string name="day2">Day 2:</string>
    <string name="lan7">Final round will be organized on last day of the event and techmart. This round will decide the final winners for each game.</string>
    <string name="r">Rules and Regulations:</string>
    <string name="ow">Only winner will be awarded with the prize.</string>
    <string name="lan8">•\tEach team of Counter Strike and FIFA will comprise of only 4 players, not less than this and not more than this.\n•\tMaximum of 4 players will be playing NFS MW at a time.\n•\tAny player caught in malpractice will be disqualified immediately.\n•\tWinner will be decided by the co-ordinator or deputy co-ordinators, and that will be final. Participant will have to accept that decision. No participant can claim the decision to be wrong as it will not be entertained no matter what.</string>
    <string name="vanand">Vishal Anand: (+91)8009417767</string>
    <string name="struct">EVENT STRUCTURE:</string>
    <string name="arjun">Round : 1 - ARJUN’S HIT</string>
    <string name="rock1">A specific range of the water rocket will be tested in this round. The rocket has to hit a provided target range marked on the ground as concentric circles. The centre of the circles lies at a distance of 50 m from the launch point.</string>
    <string name="rock2">Round : 2 - SKY SCRAPER:</string>
    <string name="rock3">The water rocket can be launched from launch pad with any suitable angle as per your convenience and would be tested for maximum time of flight. Water rockets with boosters are also allowed in this round. Multi-staging mechanism can also be implemented with or without boosters.</string>
    <string name="arena">ARENA:</string>
    <string name="rock4">The arena for the first round consists of 3 concentric circles. The centre of the circles lies at a distance of 50 m from the launch point. The circular arena is divided into 3 regions.\nRegion 1 – Circle of radius 1 .\nRegion 2 – Ring of inner radius 1 m and outer radius 2 m with same centre as circle A.\nRegion 3 – Ring of inner radius 2 m and outer radius 3 m with same centre as circle A.</string>
    <string name="rocket5">•\tThe team will be disqualified in case the bottle bursts while pressurizing and still mounted on the launcher.\n•\tParticipants are allowed to use separate models for round one and two but the same model has to be used throughout a given round.\n•\tChanges will be highlighted on the website and will also be mailed to all the registered participants. However, you are suggested to keep checking the website regularly.\n•\tThe Aero-model being used in this Competition cannot be used in any other Competition being organized in TECHMART`13\n•\tA team can consist of maximum 4 members. Students from different colleges can form a team.</string>
    <string name="eligi">Eligibility</string>
    <string name="rocket6">•\tAny student of any academic institution is eligible to participate\n•\tThe organizers reserve all rights to change any or all of the above rules.</string>
    <string name="judge">JUDGING CRITERIA</string>
    <string name="rocket7">•\tThe circular arena is divided into 3 concentric circular regions with radius of 1m, 2m and 3m.\n•\tThe object placed at centre holds 300 points\n•\tThe inner Region A (radius 1 m) holds 200 points.\n•\tThe next Region B (radius 1–2 m) holds 125 points.\n•\tThe last Region C (radius 2–3m) holds 75 points.\n•\tNO points will be awarded if the water rocket lands outside the arena.\n•\tThe position of the rocket will be the first point of impact of the rocket on the ground.\n•\tFirst round is the qualification round.\n•\tIn event of any clash of final points a tiebreaker will be held between the concerned teams. The clashing teams will have to go through round 1 until the points differ.\n•\tThe team with greater score will be awarded superior rank.\n•\tTop 10 teams will make their way to the second round.</string>
    <string name="rocket8">•\tA stopwatch will be used to measure the time of flight. The duration shall include the time when the rocket is launched and until it touches the ground in the first instance. The time for the motion of the rocket after touching the ground once is not included.\n•\tBonus 10 seconds will be added in the final time for water rocket with boosters or multi-staging. Multi-staging along with boosters will earn15 extra seconds.\n•\tHowever, it must be clearly understood that these bonus time will be awarded only on successful functioning of the mechanisms. This will be judged by the organising authority here.\n•\tSuccessful Functioning for boosters is their (all of them) detachment from the main stage and further propulsion of the main stage after that.\n•\tSuccessful Functioning for multi-stage is the separation of the various stages at different intervals.\n•\tAll decisions taken by the organising team will be deemed as final.</string>
    <string name="model">MODEL SPECIFICATION</string>
    <string name="rocket9">•\tIn the first round 3 chances will be provided out of which 1st will be a trial. The sum of last two chances will be the counted in the score.\n•\tIt is upon the participant to choose the given turn as a trial or official turn mentioning it beforehand. No points will be awarded for the trial.\n•\tParticipants will be allowed to launch their model at most 3 times in second round out of which only 2 will be considered for the final judging. The other one will be a trial.\n•\tOnly water and air can be used as propellants.\n•\tIt is not compulsory for the participants to bring their own launchers. Either they can use their own launchers or the launcher provided by organizers.\n•\tWater Rocket and any of its components should be handmade. Readymade models are strictly not allowed.\n•\tYour model can be of any size or shape and can be made of any material. But, it should not damage the arena or hurt any person. If your model is found dangerous, you will not be allowed to participate in the event.\n•\tThe water rocket may contain any of the following mechanisms suitable for different rounds\n•\tWater Rocket with Parachute mechanism.\n•\tWater rocket with booster mechanism. In this case, participants should ensure that they have proper launchers supporting the launching mechanism.\n•\tMulti-stage rocket for extended time of flight.\n•\tWater rocket with radio control mechanism.\n•\tAny other innovative mechanism will be encouraged provided that the material and mechanism used is not harmful or dangerous to any person in the field. In this case the decision of the panel of coordinators will be final and no queries will be entertained in this regard.</string>
    <string name="talent">UIET Got Talent!</string>
    <string name="ft1">The ECE department of UIET brings the first event of Robotics that will make the robots race against each other.</string>
    <string name="amar">Amar Singh (Robotics Head)</string>
    <string name="ft2">Ganesh Shankar Bhandari\nTanishka Shukla</string>
    <string name="ft3">•\tRobot must be wireless and move on wheels. The bot must not jump over any area of the arena.\n•\tDimensions of the bot(40x40x15) cm\n•\tThe arena will consist of different obstacles (concrete, mud, water, fire, sharp turns, and narrow straits). The obstacles will be placed with the maximum size of the bots in consideration.\n•\tThe bots must have a DC motor and must work on a DC battery.\n•\tOnly team registration will be entertained.\n•\tA team must comprise of 5–7 members.</string>
    <string name="gameplay">Game Play:</string>
    <string name="ft4">•\tRobots will have to cross the arena in the minimum possible time.\n•\tIf the robot causes any type of destruction in the arena, the participant will be disqualified.</string>
    <string name="ft5">Registration fees: Rs 60/- per head \nThe decision of the coordinators and the judges will be final.</string>
    <string name="ft6"><![CDATA[•\tGanesh Shankar Bhandari\n(+91) 9044899925\n•\tTanishka Shukla\n(+91) 9554934070]]></string>
    <string name="rb1">•\tThe event will comprise of a simple game of pick and place with just one exception, your bot has to do it.\n•\tRobots have to pick square and round shaped structures from one side of the arena to the other side avoiding all the hurdles.\n•\tThe structures must be placed in such a way that they form the given design.</string>
    <string name="rsp">Kapil Thakur</string>
    <string name="rb2">•\tThe robot can be wired or wireless.\n•\tThe robot must move in the arena using miniature tank tracks (chained wheels).\n•\tRobots must not skip any area on the arena\n•\tRobots must not damage the arena in any manner. In case the robot damages the arena, the participant will be disqualified.\n•\tMaximum size of the robot must be in dimensions of 35x35x40 cm\n•\tOnly team registrations will be entertained\n•\tA team may comprise of 5–7 members</string>
    <string name="rb3">There will be two rounds:\n1.\tKnockout round\n2.\tFinal round</string>
    <string name="rb4">Each team will be allotted a time limit to finish the task.</string>
    <string name="rb5">Contacts:\n•\tAmar Singh (+91)9554944070\n•\tKapil Thakur (+91)9554944070</string>
    <string name="robosoccer">Robo Soccer</string>
    <string name="ankurraj">Ankur Raj</string>
    <string name="sristi">Shrishti Singh</string>
    <string name="rs1">‘Watch the bots create “o jogo bonito”’\nIt is basically a soccer/football that will be played between two teams for a finite time.</string>
    <string name="rs2">•\tEach team can have a maximum of 5–7 members\n•\tEach team must have three bots: Two small (players), One big (goal keeper)\n•\tThe goal keeper must be efficient enough to destroy the opponent player bots that arrive towards the goal\n•\tDimension of the small bots must be 15x15x15cm\n•\tDimensions of the big (goalkeeper) bots must be 60x60x60 cm\n•\tWeight limit for the player bot and the goalkeeper bot must be 2 kg and 30 kg respectively</string>
    <string name="rs3">There will be two rounds\n•\tKnockout round\n•\tFinal round \n1.\tEach gameplay will be of 5 minutes.\n2.\tPoints will be given according to the no. of goals and destruction made by the goalkeeper to the opponent team bots.</string>
    <string name="rs4">Registration Fees: Rs 60/- per head</string>
    <string name="rs5"><![CDATA[•\tAnkur Raj (+91)9554934070\n•\tShrishti Singh (+91)9554934070]]></string>
    <string name="grid">Grid Explorer (Line Following Robot)</string>
    <string name="ge1">Ashutosh Mishra</string>
    <string name="ge2">Aparna Maurya</string>
    <string name="ge3">The bot will be a LFR (Line Following Robot) that has to follow a given design of black line on white background.</string>
    <string name="ge4">•\tThe bot has to be line follower\n•\tBot has to follow black line on a white background\n•\tIn case the bot loses the grid, the participant will be disqualified\n•\tIn case all the participants lose the grid, the participant whose bot will cover the maximum distance without distraction will be declared as the winner\n•\tOnly team registrations will be entertained\n•\tA team must comprise of 4–5 members</string>
    <string name="ge5">Bot completing the given grid of black line over a white background in the minimum time will be the winner.</string>
    <string name="rg">Registration fees: Rs 70/- per head</string>
    <string name="ge6">Contacts:\nAshutosh Mishra (+91)9554944070\nAparna Maurya (+91)9554934070</string>
    <string name="ad111">Registration Fees Rs. 40 per head</string>
    <string name="regcode">Registration Fees Rs. 30 per haed</string>
    <string name="regelc">Rgistration Fees Rs. 30 per head</string>
    <string name="elm1">An aptitude based quiz on topics related to general reasoning, computer programming and general mathematics, basic electrical engineering.</string>
    <string name="elm2">Circuit Designing on Multisim\nWe will analyse basically on the candidate’s ability to do maximum task in minimum period of time.\nPoints will be rewarded after each round and the winner will be decided on the basis of overall points scored in round 1 and round 2\nAny decision made by the coordinators and the judges will be final.</string>
    <string name="anupmishra">\nTechMart Team Mentor:\nAnup Mishra(CSE)\n</string>
    <string name="anp">Anup Mishra: (+91)9450753808</string>


</resources>
